<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arti-S Homepage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Arti-S Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Artjom Schwenk</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 14:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Volunteering for [the matrix conference] 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/volunteering-matrix2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/volunteering-matrix2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Images by Jan Michalko for the Matrix.org Foundation, CC BY-SA 4.0&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From September 19th to 22nd of this year the Matrix.org Foundation held their first own Matrix Conference in person here in Berlin. I initially found out about this, whilst scrolling through their website to learn more about the state of the project. At first I was just interested in attending the talks and to network, but then I saw that they were searching for volunteers to help them out. Now given that I&amp;rsquo;m a university student in Berlin, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t donate much to FOSS-Projects like Matrix, but I still wanted to support them. So I took my chance and volunteered as tribute from district 12.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello there! My name is Artjom Schwenk and I welcome you to my website. This is your first point of contact and a guide to finding me in the vast depths of the web. This site is also the beginning of my attempts to make a difference in the computer science and media industry. Let me introduce you to the person behind this website.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am a Russian-born German living in Berlin. I&amp;rsquo;m studying International Media and Computing (IMI) at the HTW Berlin - University of Applied Sciences. I am now entering my third semester, where I will focus on collaborative from-scratch development of applications in Java and Python. Additionally, I will concentrate on 3D design, which is one of my core interests. Other interests of mine include Linux and other free and open source software, federated social media and the gaming industry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archives</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/page/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/page/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
